Now before we go on to our actual example here let's just make sure we're clear on all the words you
现在，在我们继续我们的实际示例之前，让我们确保我们清楚您的所有单词
can write these down again.
可以再把这些写下来。
You can look these up very easily.
你可以很容易地查到这些。
These are not the only words you need to know but an on tray is often the main dish and will include
这些不是您需要知道的唯一单词，但托盘通常是主菜，包括
for example of some meat and then a couple of other things on the plate like a vegetable and then maybe
例如一些肉，然后盘子上还有一些其他的东西，比如蔬菜，然后也许
another thing like mashed potatoes and vegetables or corn and bread or some other small dish.
另一种东西，比如土豆泥和蔬菜或玉米和面包或其他一些小菜。
So usually that's called an entree.
所以通常这被称为主菜。
And so on that on a plate then you have an appetizer which is something that comes before and that's
等等放在盘子里然后你有一个开胃菜，这是之前出现的东西，那就是
meant to give you something to eat before you get your your main course.
意思是在你吃主菜之前给你吃点东西。
Your main course now main course is not something that's only used in a restaurant that's used for eating
你的主菜现在的主菜不是只在餐厅里用来吃饭的东西
in general in English.
一般用英语。
It's the main food that you eat but it's the idea of relieving your hunger right at the beginning and
这是你吃的主要食物，但它是从一开始就消除饥饿感的想法，
you'll see that usually those are a little bit cheaper and they say appetizer.
你会看到通常那些便宜一点，他们说开胃菜。
The menu is the thing you order from the wine list is also a type of menu but it's it's usually for
菜单是您从酒单中点的东西，也是一种菜单，但它通常用于
just wine and sometimes they have a drinks menu as well which is another separate menu where they have
只是酒，有时他们也有饮料菜单，这是他们有的另一个单独的菜单
alcohol so other types of alcohol might be on yet another menu.
酒精，因此其他类型的酒精可能会出现在另一个菜单上。
OK.
好的。
Just to be clear this is red wine and white wine and this might include whiskey bourbon Gin Gin and
需要说明的是，这是红葡萄酒和白葡萄酒，可能包括威士忌波旁金金酒和
Vodka cocktails and cocktails are mixed drinks.
伏特加鸡尾酒和鸡尾酒是混合饮料。
Right these are straight straight alcohol bourbon whiskey gin vodka cocktails are a mix.
对，这些是纯纯酒精波旁威士忌杜松子酒伏特加鸡尾酒是混合的。
Maybe they're sweeter.
也许他们更甜。
They have other things inside and they include whiskey bourbon gin vodka rum as well.
他们里面还有其他东西，包括威士忌波旁杜松子酒伏特加朗姆酒。
There are lots of different types of of alcohol OK a dessert actually what.
有很多不同类型的酒好一个甜点实际上是什么。
Wait a second.
等一等。
Here's my second s.
这是我的第二个。
Here's an interesting mistake that can teach us something.
这是一个有趣的错误，可以教给我们一些东西。
One way to remember the correct spelling of the word dessert is that you always want more dessert because
记住甜点这个词的正确拼写的一种方法是你总是想要更多的甜点，因为
it's sweet.
好可爱。
So you have two S's because you always want more.
所以你有两个S，因为你总是想要更多。
That's how you spell dessert.
这就是你拼写甜点的方式。
If there's one s That's dessert which is a very very dry place.
如果有一个 s 那是甜点，这是一个非常非常干燥的地方。
So this is an accident but I'm trying to use it as as a teaching point.
所以这是一个意外，但我试图将其用作教学点。
So desert is a dry place.
所以沙漠是一个干燥的地方。
It's very dry and a desert D E S S E R T V cake or pie or something sweet after you eat which is what
它很干，吃完后是甜点 D E S S E R T V 蛋糕或馅饼或甜食
I meant to write host and hostess as we talked about the person who greets you and then a waiter waitress
我的意思是写主人和女主人，因为我们谈到了向你打招呼的人，然后是女服务员
the person who brings you your food the person who will get your tips directly in a western restaurant
给你送饭的人 直接在西餐厅给你小费的人
especially in America especially in America.
尤其是在美国，尤其是在美国。
Tips are very important.
提示非常重要。
That's extra money that the waiter or waitress and also the host or hostess will get at the end of a
这是服务员或女服务员以及主人或女主人将在结束时获得的额外钱
day and they get that from money that the customers in the restaurant give.
一天，他们从餐厅顾客给的钱中得到。
They choose how much.
他们选择多少。
We'll talk about that later sides basically these things might include a small salad or another little
我们将在后面讨论，基本上这些东西可能包括一个小沙拉或另一个小
thing that you order maybe it's not an appetizer but like an appetizer that comes with your entree.
您点的东西可能不是开胃菜，而是主菜附带的开胃菜。
OK.
好的。
Catch of the day.
当天的渔获。
Sometimes you'll see this catch.
有时你会看到这个问题。
It's for fishing.
是用来钓鱼的。
So this is going to be a fish.
所以这将是一条鱼。
Whatever fish they have.
不管他们有什么鱼。
This is going to be the catch of the day.
这将是当天的收获。
This is what they have today.
这就是他们今天所拥有的。
Dressing dressing is a kind of sauce.
调料 调料是一种酱料。
There are many different types of dressing.
有许多不同类型的敷料。
It goes on salad.
它放在沙拉上。
Put it on your salad.
把它放在你的沙拉上。
So if you order a salad you might get a thousand island you might get Italian you might get vinaigrette
所以如果你点沙拉，你可能会得到一千个岛，你可能会得到意大利，你可能会得到香醋
vinaigrette is my favorite.
香醋是我的最爱。
OK and then toppings might be for a salad.
好的，然后浇头可能是沙拉。
These are things that you add to the top of the salad maybe extra like cheese like onions like other
这些是你添加到沙拉顶部的东西，可能更像奶酪，像洋葱，像其他的一样
vegetables and also for example if you order a pizza you also maybe add toppings.
蔬菜，例如，如果您订购比萨饼，您还可以添加配料。
So the cheese is usually not considered a topping on a pizza because that's an important part of pizza.
所以奶酪通常不被认为是披萨的配料，因为这是披萨的重要组成部分。
Green peppers and onions and black olives or sausage or whatever else you like to put on that.
青椒、洋葱、黑橄榄或香肠或任何你喜欢放的东西。
That is called a topping toppings.
这就是所谓的浇头浇头。
OK.
好的。
As we talked about a reservation or a booking but at a restaurant it's usually called a reservation.
正如我们所说的预订或预订，但在餐厅通常称为预订。
When you call before and you get a time and pasta is a very popular thing at Western restaurants especially
当你之前打电话，你有时间，意大利面是西餐厅很受欢迎的东西，尤其是
in America.
在美国。
They might often have some kind of pasta.
他们可能经常有某种面食。
This is basically noodles but it's Italian style noodles and there are many different forms of that.
这基本上是面条，但它是意大利风格的面条，有很多不同的形式。
And it's not only noodles.
它不仅仅是面条。
Actually many different forms it's a special thing that's basically only Italian and noodles are always
实际上有很多不同的形式，这是一个特别的东西，基本上只有意大利面，面条总是
long and thin.
又长又瘦。
Pasta is not always long and thin.
意大利面并不总是又长又薄。
All right.
好的。
So those are some words I just want to make sure you know and I'm sure you know many of those.
所以这些是我想让你知道的一些词，我相信你知道其中的很多。
But I just want to make sure you know those before we go on to our example.
但在我们继续我们的例子之前，我只是想确保你知道这些。